[
  {
    "question": 'Neither Ade nor the students _____ around.',
    "option1": 'is',
    'option2': 'was',
    'option3': 'are',
    'option4': 'am',
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': 'None of you ____ righteous.',
    'option1': 'is',
    'option2': 'was',
    'option3': 'has ever been',
    'option4': 'are',
    'answer': 4
  },
  {
    'question': 'None of them ____ righteous; said Ade.',
    'option1': 'were',
    'option2': 'is',
    'option3': 'are',
    'option4': 'have ever been',
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': 'Seventy percent of the problem ____ solved.',
    'option1': 'have been',
    'option2': 'has being',
    'option3': 'has been',
    'option4': 'have being',
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': 'John welcomed his guests ____ offered them drinks.',
    'option1': 'and',
    'option2': 'while',
    'option3': 'until',
    'option4': 'as',
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': 'Two year ago, I _____ English in England.',
    'option1': 'studied',
    'option2': 'was study',
    'option3': 'was reading',
    'option4': 'read',
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': 'You _____ eating when i arrived.',
    'option1': 'was',
    'option2': 'are',
    'option3': 'were',
    'option4': 'have been',
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': 'He did his best.',
    'option1': "didn't she?",
    'option2': 'does he?',
    'option3': "isn't he",
    'option4': "didn't he?",
    'answer': 4
  },
  {
    'question': 'You or I as a child of God, ____ to prosper',
    'option1': 'is',
    'option2': 'has',
    'option3': 'are',
    'option4': 'am',
    'answer': 4
  },
  {
    'question': 'He has successfully _____ his online form.',
    'option1': 'submit',
    'option2': 'submitted',
    'option3': 'submited',
    'option4': 'submet',
    'answer': 2
  },
]
